[
    {
        "qid": 610248,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "49%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 212278,
        "question": "Patient is a 74 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "63%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 715380,
        "question": "Patient is a 3 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, upper chest, and right breast.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option3": "Sarcoidosis",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "95%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 658849,
        "question": "Patient is a 16 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The patient's pain is at an intensity of 7 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Epiglottitis",
        "option3": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 593484,
        "question": "Patient is a 26 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of their head.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 7 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Anemia",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 25777,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, upper chest, right breast, and left breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 5 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Sarcoidosis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 755785,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive, like a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest and upper chest.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Myocarditis",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "57%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 748317,
        "question": "Patient is a 65 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has recently experienced a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 204885,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 2 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has a cough.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Acute otitis media",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 34750,
        "question": "Patient is a 7 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sharp.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "64%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1152656,
        "question": "Patient is a 50 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or feels palpitations.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 754482,
        "question": "Patient is a 49 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, palate, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.",
        "option1": "Unstable angina",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 64131,
        "question": "Patient is a 8 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, side of the chest (right), side of the chest (left), and posterior chest wall (right).<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 910264,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 478481,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating very irregularly or in a disorganized pattern.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option4": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]